So this sentence, how much loan banks can offer you. You stay home, not CDC.
This sentence can be better. This is your main eligibility criteria. I don't know.
The sentence can be better. The problem with this sentence is that the sets don't work.
I have come here to see why you should cut your monthly income.
Why do you want my monthly income?
Tell me, what does your monthly income work in loan processing?
And yes, you can stay home, not CDC.
What does monthly income work in loan processing?
That's what sets how much bank loan works.
But...
Ceiling won the loan against this house.
No one in India knows about ceilings.
Sets the ceilings.
All the properties are in this house.
Let's talk about it.
Because...
Our requirements have been captured in this.
So we have to change the loop.
This sentence starts with sets.
And the word ceiling doesn't work in India.
What I want to know is that property agreement value...
How does the loan get affected?
Which value should I set?
And...
I want to say that...
What I feel is that...
My property is 8 crores.
But it is actually 8 crores.
So I want to say that...
Actually...
Property agreement value...
Either...
If you have a recent purchase, you get the value of your registrar's agreement.
Or...
Independent loan assessment is done.
And it is usually less than market value.
So you put a little conservative value.
You think it costs 1 crore to get a better estimate.
But the title of the agreement value...
But the agreement is 8 crores.
The new agreement...
Can be the registry value.
The property's agreement value.
Who takes the loan from the old one?
The amount on the agreement is white.
The independent valuation...
The banks do it for them.
Yes.
The agreement value makes sense.
Otherwise, who would take the registry?
Then I don't care.
I want the property agreement value.
He knows what we do.
You need to keep the property value here.
Only the property value?
Yes.
Then he has to go over the issue.
He knows the agreement value.
Property agreement value...
Makes me think about property.
Agreement value.
Property value according to the agreement.
This is also good.
But the property agreement value is complex.
Like we overload adjectives.
Because you have to tell that...
You have to show the value of the property.
Which one is the agreement?
The official property value.
Should I click on i?
Official means...
If you want to make an agreement...
How much is the official property value?
How much is the official value?
How much is the agreement?
The bank also asks how much is the agreement?
How much is the registry value?
There are two words.
Agreement and registry.
If you just put the agreement value, which agreement?
Property value according to the agreement.
Then remove the value and put the amount.
That is the value.
Property agreement value is complex.
Property value according to the agreement is easy.
But according to the agreement, the input box...
As per agreement.
Five characters extra mark.
I think it should be quick.
Five letters.
No, no.
The agreement value is...
Very complex.
Property agreement value.
How do you know that?
Property value according to the agreement.
The value is property.
Property is agreement value?
No, that's it.
I think it should be like this.
Property is value as per agreement.
Okay, I'll take a small one.
Six characters as per agreement.
As per agreement.
Okay, I'll take a small one.
What small?
Property agreement value.
Property is value as per agreement.
Okay, I'll take a small one.